improveyourlunchlife.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy – Campbell Soup Company

**Campbell Soup Company Privacy Policy – PLEASE NOTE THAT AS OF 10/28/2007 WE HAVE MADE CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

This website is owned and operated by Campbell Soup Company. 

Here at Campbell, we recognize that many visitors to our sites are concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. So we've developed a Privacy Policy to address this sensitive area. This policy is effective as of 10/28/07. We may from time to time update this policy and invite you to review this page periodically. In the event this policy changes, we will inform you by posting an updated policy on this web page. All changes will go into effect on the date that is posted in our policy. The new policy will apply to all past and current users of this site and will replace any prior policies. 

Some of our sites may be directed in whole or in part to children under the age of 13. Our policy regarding these sites is described below under the heading “Children's Privacy Policy.” In addition, not all of our websites are subject to this policy. Please see the list of affiliated websites not subject to this policy listed under the heading “Links to Other Sites.” Whenever we refer to our “sites” in this policy, we mean only those sites subject to this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or our Children's Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: 

Campbell Soup Company  
Campbell Place  
Camden, NJ 08103-1701  
Attention: Legal Department  
or Global Advertising Department  
1-800-257-8443

Our offices are open from 9 a.m. - 7 p.m. Eastern Time, Monday through Friday. Please feel free to email us anytime by visiting our Consumer Response Center. We'll be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns. 

**Our Policy**  
At our sites, we do not collect personally-identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not require you to register or provide information to us in order to view any of our sites. If you register in order to use one or more of the many features of our sites, in addition to other purposes described in this Privacy Policy, we use the information you supply for the purpose of providing the services you've requested. These features may include: 

• Opt in email like Meal Mail  
• Send to a friend  
• Recipe Box  
• Discussion board like the Kitchen Table 

Depending on the feature you have registered to use, we may collect one or more of the following types of personally-identifiable information: name, address, phone number, email address, username and password. If you do not provide this information, you may not be able to register for that or other features on the site. You can always access and review your personally-identifiable information by visiting any of the sites on which you have registered. In addition, you can correct factual errors in your personally-identifiable information by editing your profile on any of our sites. 

Creating, viewing and editing your personally-identifiable information can only be done with a valid member-provided user id and password. 

If you specifically agree to follow-up contacts by us or ask to be put on our mailing list when you register, we may contact you from time to time. You can always change your preference for follow-up contacts or opt out of any further contacts or services just by e-mailing us at any time or by visiting the area of the site where you registered. However, unless you specifically register to receive communication from a site, that site will not contact you. 

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we don't share the information you give us with anyone outside of the Campbell Soup Company family of companies. In certain instances, we may disclose your personally-identifiable information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, Campbell Soup Company or others. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe the law requires it. In the event of a merger, consolidation or sale or transfer of all or substantially all of our company or its assets, it is possible that all user information collected by this site will be transferred to the purchaser or the new company. 

We may use the personal information you provide us to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; to statistically analyze website usage; and to improve our features and the content of our sites. You would never be opted into a service you did not request. 

We may also use your personal information to customize the content that our sites deliver to you. For example, we may customize the recipes, product information and promotions we deliver to you based upon the information you have previously provided to us. 

As an added convenience to you, when you register on anyone of our sites, your id and password can be used across the family of Campbell sites. Visit the Our Brands page, on campbellsoupcompany.com, for a list of our sites. 

**Cookies**  
Like most companies, we use “cookie” technology on our sites to collect aggregate information. When you log into one of our sites, the cookie tells us whether you've visited us before or are a new visitor. This allows us to measure the appeal of our sites to new and return visitors. The cookie doesn't track any personal information about you or provide us with any way to contact you, and the cookie doesn't extract any information from your computer. Cookies are simply the best way for us to be able to offer you the most enjoyable and hassle-free online environment. 

**Contests and Sweepstakes**  
Our sites sometimes include notices of contests, sweepstakes or other promotions we are conducting, and we may permit you to participate electronically in some cases. If that occurs, we will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the contest, sweepstakes or promotion (e.g., to contact you if you're a winner). In addition, we may participate in internet related promotions sponsored by reputable third parties. In these instances, if you are a participant in such promotions, we may provide certain personally-identifiable information to these third parties in furtherance of the promotion. These parties have agreed to hold this information in confidence, not use it for any purpose except to carry out the requested service, and honor Campbell's privacy and security policies in the way this information is handled. 

**Questionnaires and Surveys**  
From time to time, our sites may also be conducting questionnaires and surveys. Survey information will be treated like all of the information we collect, and it is used to help us improve the appeal of our products and our sites. 

**Third Parties Service Providers**  
We sometimes employ other companies and individuals to perform services for us. For example, we hire agencies to help administer consumer promotions, to analyze data, to fulfill orders you place, and to provide customer service. These parties are required to maintain any personal information they receive from you in confidence and may only use it in connection with the services they are providing to us. 

**When you Shop with Us**  
If you shop with us via our website, we collect the following information: name, address, phone number, email address, billing information including credit card number and expiration date as well as information such as an alternative address for shipping purposes. We only use your name, address, phone number, billing information/credit card information to process your order. The email address you provide is used for internal purposes only, such as confirming and tracking your order. We may also contact you via email or regular mail from time-to-time to keep you up-to-date on the latest news or to send you our latest offerings. If you previously opted-in for email communication and no longer wish to receive marketing emails from us, please opt-out by visiting the area of the site where you registered or you may email us at any time. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
Our sites may contain links to other sites, including other sites that are owned or operated by our affiliates or us. While we do our best to make sure that every link to a non-affiliated site sends you to a helpful place on the internet, we cannot guarantee the content of these non-affiliated sites. The non-affiliated sites will always have their own privacy policies. In addition, some of our affiliated sites also have their own privacy policies and are not subject to this policy. These affiliated sites include, but are not limited to: campbellsoup.ca; campbells-soup.ru; campbellsoup.com.sg; campbellsoup.com.my; campbellsoup.com.mx; campbellsoup.com.au; campbellsoup.de; campbellsoup.be; campbellsoup.fi; campbellsoup.se; campbellsoup.com.hk; campbellsoup.co.jp; campbellawayfromhome.com; stockpot.com;; erasco.de; heisse-tasse.de; raguletto.de; aiki.be; devoslemmens.be; royco.be; arnotts.com; labelsforeducation.ca; and gardennay.com. You should always check the privacy policy of the specific site you're visiting to understand your rights. 

**Security**  
Campbell takes your privacy and security seriously, for this reason we have established physical security measures including locked doors and files, electronic security and managerial controls that limit the potential for misuse of information by employees and contractors. 

**Children's Privacy Policy**

_Children's Privacy Policy -- General_

Some of our sites may be directed in whole or in part to children under the age of 13. Generally, we do not directly or indirectly collect personally-identifiable information from children under the age of 13 in these areas. On some sites, children are allowed to send preprogrammed messages to friends regarding a particular feature of the site. In these instances, the child is prompted to enter the email addresses of his or her friends and some other non-identifiable information, such as his or her initials. This information is automatically discarded as soon as the preprogrammed message is delivered. From time to time, however, we may request limited personally-identifiable information in order to conduct online contests or sweepstakes. Our practices with respect to collection of personally-identifiable information from children under the age of 13 are described below. We do not condition a child's participation in an activity on the child's disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to engage in the activity. In addition, a parent may at anytime review any personally-identifiable information collected about their child under the age of 13, have this information deleted and prohibit further collection or use of the child's information (although this may require the child to forfeit any prize won in a sweepstakes or contest). 

_Children's Privacy Policy - Information Collected in Contests and Sweepstakes_

Some of our sites directed in whole or in part to children under the age of 13 occasionally offer contests and/or sweepstakes. **Our contests and sweepstakes are designed in such a manner that a child under the age of 13 is not required to provide any personally- identifiable information about him/herself (other than a parent's e-mail address) prior to being named a winner.** To participate in these contests or sweepstakes, however, we may require the child to provide a screen name and a parent's e-mail address. We send an email to the parent notifying the parent that his/her child wishes to participate in the contest or sweepstakes. The parent has the option to withhold his/her consent to the child's participation. If the parent does not withhold his/her consent and the child is a potential winner of a prize in the sweepstakes or contest, the child is required to print a form requesting, among other things, the parent (and not the child) to provide the information necessary to award the prize, such as the child's name, address, social security number and other personally identifiable information. The parent is required to sign this form and return it to us. 

The parental email address collected from each child is used solely to obtain parental consent, and it is not provided to any third party except those third parties we have engaged to assist us in running the contest or sweepstakes. These third parties are required to maintain the parental email in confidence and may only use it in connection with the services they are providing to us. The information collected from winners may be (i) used in advertising and promotional activities relating to our contest and/or sweepstakes, which may include making certain of this information publicly available, and (ii) passed on to third parties for the purpose of awarding prizes, and, depending on the type of prize, these third parties may not be prohibited from using the information for purposes other than awarding the prize (such as marketing or advertising). **Again, please note that personally-identifiable information (other than a parent's address) is only collected from the parents of children under the age of 13 who have potentially won a prize, and only after the parent consents to the award of the prize and the disclosure of the information**. 

_Children's Privacy Policy - Contact Information_

If you have any questions about our Children's Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at the address, phone number or e-mail address listed at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

Revision History: September 2003, March 2003, August 2002, October 2007
